segway.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy - Segway

#### Privacy Policy

Date of Last Revision: February 21, 2008 

###### Privacy

We value your privacy. 

###### Privacy Statement

Protecting your privacy is a Segway Inc. ("Segway") top priority. This statement discloses the information practices for Segway's web sites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. By visiting [www.segway.com](http://www.segway.com/) and its respective subdomains (i.e. [social.segway.com](http://social.segway.com/)), collectively "the Site", you accept the practices described in this Privacy Statement, as modified from time to time by us. 

What kinds of Information we collect and how we use it 

  * #### Registration, Interactive Forms, and User Content

**[www.segway.com](http://www.segway.com/)** : A user may wish to register on **www.segway.com** to receive informational and promotional email materials such as newsletters, product release announcements and participate in surveys. Users may also use a form to submit feedback to our site or to contact us. 

For ordinary users, only a name and email address is requested for these interactions. For business users, we also request additional information about the business, including the company name, address, and phone number. All such contacts and registrations are voluntary on the part of the user; therefore, the user has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. 

**[social.segway.com](http://social.segway.com/)** : A user may wish to register on **social.segway.com** to form relationships, share photos, send messages, perform searches and queries, form groups, set up events, receive information and promotional email materials such as newsletters, participate in surveys, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your contact list. Segway may also use information gathered here to extend personalized offers at its discretion. 

For registrants, we will request the following information: name, city, state, zip code, country, email address, Segway model info, serial number, and usage information. All such registration information is voluntary on the part of the registrant. The registrant has the choice whether to register. You post User Content (as defined in the Segway Social Site Terms of Use) on the **social.segway.com** site at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on **social.segway.com** will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on **social.segway.com**. You understand and agree that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content. 

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on **social.segway.com** is a violation of the Segway Social Site Terms of Use and should be reported to privacy [at] segway [dot] com. 

  * #### Information Collection and Use

If you request something from Segway, such as service, a callback, specific marketing materials, or feedback, we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. To help us do this, we may share relevant information with others such as shipping carriers, product orientation providers, and marketing advisors. We may also contact you as a part of our customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes. 

  * #### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Segway does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated entities except: (i) as provided above; (ii) to provide services you have requested when we have your permission; or (iii) under the following circumstances: 

    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the site's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of Segway under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Segway communicate with you about offers and marketing. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
    * We transfer information about you if Segway is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Segway will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * #### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data that often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a web site's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser, if your browser's preferences allow it, but to protect your privacy, your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies stored on your computer by other sites. 

Segway uses cookies to store your user ID on your computer, allowing use of interactive areas on our Site. The cookie is placed on your computer only when you log into interactive sections of our Site and is removed once you have closed your web browser. 

You can configure your web browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the Help menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) You may reject all cookies sent to you without experiencing any loss of web site functionality. 

###### Security

Segway takes every reasonable precaution to protect our users' information both online and off-line. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

###### Links and Business Relationships

The Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Segway is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Site. 

###### Correcting/Updating Personal Information

**www.segway.com** : If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your postal code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. 

**social.segway.com** : If you are a registrant who wishes to change your profile, you may modify your profile on **social.segway.com**. 

###### Choice/Opt-in

Our users are given the opportunity to opt-in to having their information used for purposes not directly related to our Site (such as receiving our occasional e-mail newsletter) on the Site's registration pages. 

Users of www.segeway.com who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials (such as information on products, services, special deals) may stop receiving these communications by emailing us at unsubscribe [at] segway [dot] com. 

Registrants at **social.segway.com** who no longer wish to receive information from Segway may check the box so indicating. 

###### Children

**www.segway.com** is a general audience site that is not designed nor intended to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. To respect the privacy of children and to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), children under the age of 13 should not provide any personal information on this site. We ask that parents supervise their children while online. 

**social.segway.com** is a general audience site that is not designed nor intended to collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not attempt to register on **social.segway.com** or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under the age of 18 may provide any personal information to or on **social.segway.com**. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a person under the age of 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We ask that parents supervise their children while online. This web site is not designed nor intended for anyone under the age of 16. If you are 16 years of age, you may view this web site, but you may not register on this site. 

###### Notification of Changes

Segway reserves the right to update and change this Privacy Policy at our discretion. If we do this, we will post the new Privacy Policy on this page and will indicate at the top of the page the date the policy was last revised. You should review this Privacy Policy for any changes each time you visit **www.segway.com** or **social.segway.com**. If you feel that Segway is not abiding by this Privacy Statement, you should first contact Segway by sending an email to privacy [at] segway [dot] com.
